tucando.com 2012-03-17

# Tucando.com - Free Business Directory - Free Advertising.

Online Privacy Policy

**Tucando**

This privacy policy applies to all personal information collected by Tucando via the internet.

Tucando recognises the importance of your privacy, and that you have a right to control how your personal information is collected and used. We know that providing personal information is an act of trust and we take that seriously. Unless you directly give us consent to do otherwise, Tucando will only collect and use your personal information as set out below.

**Collection of information**

The four main ways we collect personal information about you are:

when information about you is posted on a Tucando website, either by you or by a third party;

when you log into a Tucando website or otherwise submit personal information to Tucando;

when you use a Tucando website, in which case our system automatically collects information relating to your visit to that website, such as your IP address;

The type of information that we collect from you may include the following: your name, phone number, address, email address, company position/title, credit card details, IP address, cookies, personal information that you include in your business listing or personal information that you email/send using email functionality on the Bizebees.com website.

**Our use of cookies**

Cookies are pieces of information that a website transfers to your computer's hard disk for record keeping purposes. Most web browsers are set to accept cookies.Tucando uses cookies to make your use of our website and services as convenient as possible. Cookies in and of themselves do not personally identify users, although they do identify a user's browser. Cookies are useful to estimate our number of users and determine overall traffic patterns through our website. If you do not wish to receive any cookies you may set your browser to refuse cookies. This may mean you will not be able to take full advantage of Tucando's services.

**Using and disclosing your personal information**

Our purpose in collecting information about you is to:

provide you with a better service experience with content and advertising that is more relevant to your interests; and

create a business information database for use as part of Tucando's online business. Whilst Tucando's business information database is designed to operate as a business directory (not a directory of individuals) it is possible that personal information may become included in the business information database.

Tucando will not use or disclose any information about you without your consent, unless:

the use or disclosure is for one of the purposes described above or otherwise permitted by this policy;

it is required or permitted by law (including by relevant privacy laws);

we believe it necessary to provide you with a service which you have requested;

to protect the rights, property or personal safety of another Tucando website user, any member of the public or Tucando; or any of the assets and/or operations of Tucando are being transferred to another party.

If you do not provide requested information, Tucando may not be able to provide you with access to or full use of sections of the Tucando website.

**Disclosing information**

Sometimes, the activities described above require us to share your personal information with other organisations. The types of situations in which Tucando usually discloses personal information, and the types of organisations to which such disclosure is usually made, include the following:

The business information database is available via the internet to any member of the public. It is also disclosed in its entirety to Tucando's related entities and to other entities with whom Tucando has a business relationship, as part of **Tucando's online business.**

Catch discloses personal information to its service providers, advisers and other entities with whom Tucando has a business relationship, in the course of operating the Tucando websites and Tucando online business and in the course of delivering the Tucando services.

**Marketing**

In seeking to give you the most worthwhile experience of our websites possible, Tucando may use your personal information to send you information and product updates about Tucando websites and services, or other products and services, or to permit other parties to send other information about products or services which may be of interest to you.

We may contact you at any email or other address or contact point which we have collected or obtained in order to:

contact you about your business listing on a Tucando website;

provide you with updated information about Tucando websites; or

provide you with other information about other products or services which you may enjoy.

If you are receiving promotional information from Tucando and do not wish to receive this information any longer, you may remove your name from our list by contacting the tucando.com and asking to be removed from our mailing list. Please allow 28 days for this request to be processed.

Access to the information we hold

You can request access to the personal information we hold about you by making a request to the Tucando. We will provide you with access unless we are legally authorised not to do so.

Changing and deleting the information we have about you

If at any time you wish to change personal information that is inaccurate or out of date, please contact us by emailing Tucando. If you wish to have your personal information deleted, please let us know in the same manner as referred to above. We will take all reasonable steps to change or delete information in response to such a request. If there is a reason that we cannot make that change or deletion, we will inform you of that reason.

Storage and security of your personal information

Tucando will endeavour to take all reasonable steps to keep secure any information which we hold about you, and to keep this information accurate and up to date. You should note that the internet is not a secure method of transmitting information and, as such, we are not responsible for the security of any information sent or received over the internet.

Please note that Tucando may use overseas facilities including but not limited to in the US, to store, process or back up its information. As a result, we may transfer your personal information to our overseas facilities. However, this does not change our commitment to keep your information secure.

**Third party websites**

Tucando websites contain links to websites that are not operated by Tucando and the contact details for many businesses not operated by Tucando. These linked sites and listed businesses are not under the control of Tucando, and we are not responsible for the conduct of those businesses. Before disclosing your personal information on any other website or to any other company, we advise you to examine the Terms and Conditions / Privacy Policy of those organisations.

**Privacy inquiries**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or how Tucando deals with your personal information you can contact: tucando.com

**Future changes**

Our commitment to being a leading provider of online business directory services means that our business will continue to evolve as we introduce new services and features. Because of this, from time to time, our policies will be reviewed and may be revised. Tucando reserves the right to change its Privacy Policy at any time and notify you by posting an updated version on each Tucando website. The amended Privacy Policy will apply between us whether or not we have given you specific notice of any change.
